Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[funky hip-hop beat layers in]
[older Kanan]
Previously on Raising Kanan...
I need the cash.
and I need it now.
You find someone to take
this shit off my hands.
and I'll make sure you get
a nice cut of the dough.
I may have a buyer
from overseas.
-who'd be interested in it.
-[camera clicking]
Who's supplying your horse?
You just want my heron connect?
Why the fuck didn't just ask?
Why we got to go
through all this?
-[gun clicks]
-[panting]
Now give me the fucking name.
or I'ma load this shit up.
My parents are saying
I can never see you again.
Your parents are right. Aisha.
you shouldn't be with me.
Those police
still trying to scare you?
They said another neighbor
saw a Black guy
coming out of the house.
What you do?
Guess I'ma need you to get
the cop to look into it.
Anything Baptiste touched
is potentially tainted.
I didn't know they were
gonna have him killed.
-Who made the call?
-Ishmael and Stephanie Henry.
-Snaps and Pop.
-They killed Fame?
With some help from the police.
And no side hustles
this time around. Breeze.
Your work is our work.
-Who are you?
-Y'all fucking with me now.
I kept my dad from
beatin' you to fuckin' death
because I thought-
I thought maybe there
was more to this.
You ain't about shit. Kanan.
I panicked.
I didn't know what to do.
Nah. you ain't panic.
you protected Kanan.
I'm all fucked up out here.
Lou-Lou.
I don't even know
what I'm doin'.
Anybody fucks with my
tenants. they fuck with me.
We already cut Raq
off at the knees.
I want her cut off
at the fucking neck.
We have found another partner.
You fuckin' with
Stefano and all of them?
He makin' you kick
me to the curb.
You don't know shit
about where I'm from.
You about to find out.
How many more wars you
tryin' to have at the same time?
As many as it take to win.
-I don't have time for this.
-Ain't gonna take long.
[gunshots]
You gon' put down Raq?
It's about showin'
who the fuck we are.
-I appreciate the opportunity.
-Best of luck Jarita.
You. too.
You workin' with Raq?
I got beef with her.
And who the fuck are you.
exactly?
Her son.
♪ I'm a hustla. baby ♪
-♪ I'm a hustla. baby ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I know heartbreaks
Setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through
The ups and downs ♪
♪ You know I get around ♪
♪ So to me. it's all a part
Of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke man
Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure. man
I gotta take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turn homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Make money
Make-make-make money ♪
♪ When shit hit the fan
We'll take money. Southside ♪
♪ Beef with the best of 'em
Done shot at the rest of 'em ♪
♪ Checks. I'm collectin' 'em
Check. boy. I'm finessin' 'em ♪
♪ Big bags of bread ♪
♪ Boy. you fuck around
Put a big bag on your head ♪
♪ 'Fore the weather break
You're dead ♪
♪ Let's get to it ♪
♪ They don't do it
Like we do it ♪
♪ Cop it. whip it
Bag it. flip it ♪
♪ Re-up. we up
G'd up. what up? ♪
♪ Runnin' 'round this bitch
Still not givin' a fuck ♪
♪ When it come to that paper
There'll be no complications ♪
♪ Ha-ha. that's right ♪
♪ Put a hole in a nigga
Right in front of you ♪
♪ Your heartbeat pacin' ♪
♪ And it's alright ♪
♪ That's how we do it
On this side ♪
♪ Niggas get to it
♪ I know heartbreaks
Setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through
The ups and downs ♪
♪ You know I get around ♪
♪ So to me. it's all a part
Of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke man
Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure. man
I gotta take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turn homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Ayy. ayy ♪
[Rileyy vocalization]
[melancholy music playing]
[older Kanan]
When you hustlin'.
you ain't thinkin'
about nobody but you.
You tellin' yourself it's for
all your peoples. your family.
but fuck outta here
with all that.
This about you. nigga.
Always been about you.
But when shit get ill.
that's when you start
thinkin' about your people.
You worry they gonna
pay for what you did.
That they gonna die
behind your bullshit.
So you don't sleep. don't eat.
damn near don't even breathe.
And you keep asking yourself
the same shit
over and over and over again.
What the fuck did I do?
She and her brother must die.
Well. look. first let
me express my condolences.
I mean. when you're
in our line of work. we-
We often lose sight
of the-the human cost.
And. frankly. that's-that's
the highest price we pay.
So I'm-I'm sorry for your loss.
and it's a fucking tragedy.
I am concerned
that killing her might offend
your colleague in Manhattan.
And I don't want
that kind of trouble.
Without you and the Colombian.
Raq's business is done.
Fini. Kaput.
And if her business is dead.
she's of no use to
Pino Bernardi.
[chuckles]
If you ain't a paycheck
for Pino.
you ain't worth his while.
Let me handle her. Hafiz.
I owe Raq and her brother
bullets to the head
for quite a while.
Time to pay off that debt.
[dramatic music playing]
John.
[Raq]
She tell you what it's about?
Just said we need to meet.
You hittin' that?
I keep tellin' you.
ain't nothin' like that been
goin' on between me and Flossie.
Ain't no judgment here. nigga.
Just tryin' to see if you got
a close enough connect to her
that could help us smooth out
any shit that might be rough.
We just talk. that's all.
Here she come.
[clears throat]
How can anyone live
anywhere but New York?
I don't get it.
So your son broke into
my apartment last night.
I don't know if he was there
to kill me or scare me.
and I don't care
one way or the other.
Look. Kanan just a confused.
angry kid who...
He told me he swapped out
those drugs
that killed the judge.
And he also told me
that you knew.
You lied to me.
Did you know?
We're done.
I've already let
Pino Bernardi know.
I'm gonna miss talking
to you. Marvin.
Our conversations
meant a lot to me.
Me too.
This shit can be fixed.
Your brother is the only
reason you're not dead already.
So don't press your luck.
[dramatic music playing]
Your girl just fucked us.
Nah. we fucked ourselves.
I told you I was
gonna scare her.
That's what I did.
But you didn't scare her. Kanan.
You pissed her off.
And Flossie Siegal ain't
someone you wanna piss off.
I wanted her to stop
working with Raq.
and that's what she gon' do.
And she was real clear she
wasn't gon' do nothin' to you.
You good.
You said that you and me
are the same. but we not.
I'm not like you.
I'm not like this.
The fuck did you think
was gon' happen
when I walked in there
with my gat out?
I don't know. I don't know
why I started helping you
with this shit
in the first place.
This whole thing with you
has fucked with my head.
You was all sweet and nice
to me.
I didn't. I didn't.
I didn't believe it.
I didn't believe you.
But then once you told me
you was playin' me.
I started to trust you.
Treat me good and
I don't trust you.
Lie to me and I do.
What the fuck does
that say about me?
I mean.
how much do I hate myself?
Obviously. I think
that I deserve to be lied to.
deserve to be played with.
treat me like shit
and I'll even help
you set up my boss.
who kills people.
Like I said. Flossie ain't gonna
do shit to you. Jarita.
But I ain't got time to listen
to all this noise right now.
Fuck you. Kanan.
Fuck you too. bitch.
That shit between us
wasn't ever real anyway.
♪♪♪
We gonna hit that pawnshop.
Knock that shit
to the fuckin' ground!
Fuck Stefano. fuck Snaps.
fuck Pop. fuck Breeze.
fuck all of 'em.
Fuck Kanan too. though.
We go in blastin' and he there.
he gonna get dropped.
See. you want to be at war
with all these niggas.
but you real choosy
on who we killin'.
Kanan still a kid. Marvin.
He don't know what
the fuck he doin'.
D-Wiz was a kid.
So was that bike nigga
we put down.
And Scrap wasn't even much older
than Kanan.
Don't seem like you got a issue
killin' other people kids.
You wanna kill your nephew?
Is that what you want?
I don't want nothin'
to do with none of this shit.
But I'm in too deep now
to get the fuck out.
so. I'ma follow your lead.
until we get to wherever
the fuck we goin'.
Hit the pawn shop
and bring Kanan to me.
You'd do the same shit
if it was Juke.
♪♪♪
[door closes]
This shit is a fuckin' mess.
Detective Garcia.
Come on in.
♪♪♪
Just got word.
The Thomases are fair game.
Raq and her brother
ain't got no friends no more.
So it's open season.
Stefano wants us to handle it.
But you and Kanan
gon' do the work.
It's Kanan's fam. though.
It's a lot to ask.
This will be a good
measuring stick for him.
Young Kanan is always
sayin' he's with us.
Time to put some walk
behind all that talk.
You gon' take out Raq.
Don't wanna take a chance
on Kanan freezin' up
when it comes to his mother.
But we gonna insist that
Kanan pull a trigger here.
We need to see how committed
and dedicated he really is.
Kanan's with us. man.
That don't necessarily mean
he gone be cool
with droppin' his own peoples.
We his peoples now.
He got a problem with it.
then he's the problem.
And Kanan knows
how we handle problems.
[tense music playing]
A number of people say
that they saw you having
a heated conversation
with Captain Baptiste
at his retirement party.
In light of his suicide.
we're wondering what
the subject matter
of that conversation
was and whether it might
give us some sense of Captain
Baptiste's mental state.
Honestly. I don't even remember.
We were just talking shit.
Baptiste owed me some money off
some bet we made on the Jets.
and I was giving him
a hard time about it.
That's all.
Captain Baptiste
gamble regularly?
No. no. it wasn't
anything like that.
It was for dinner at
Peter Luger or some bullshit.
Captain Baptiste was under
investigation for corruption
by our office as well as the
F.B.I.. Detective Garcia.
Any insight on him
that you might be able to
provide us would be invaluable.
Get the hell out of here.
Baptiste was about as
by the book as you get.
[chuckles]
Depends on what book
you're talking about.
Look.
Captain Baptiste was good to me.
I don't have a bad word
to say about him.
Far as I'm concerned.
he was a great cop
and an even better man.
♪♪♪
[dramatic music playing]
[heavy breathing]
[indistinct conversations]
[arcade game playing
in background]
♪♪♪
Thought you didn't want
to fuck with me no more.
I don't.
but I know who killed Fame.
Is was Snaps and Pop.
They was worried he was
talkin' to the police.
Where you hear that?
I got somebody who knows.
The shit's true.
You down to make this right
for Fame. or not?
♪♪♪
I just told you
that I know who killed
your best friend.
and you ain't got nothin'
to say?
You told me before
I wasn't about shit.
now you lookin' for an assist.
I ain't lookin' for shit. nigga.
I'm just tryin' to give you
the chance
to get payback for your boy.
-Fame always talked too much.
-The fuck that mean?
That mean.
if you out here snitchin'.
you gon' pay a price.
If Fame was talkin'.
he got what he deserve.
He was your best fuckin' friend.
I ain't worryin'
about niggas who gone.
Niggas who gone
like Uncle Lou. you mean?
[dramatic music playing]
♪♪♪
[siren wailing in distance]
["The Good Life"
by Tony Bennett playing]
♪ Lets you hide
all the sadness you feel ♪
♪ You won't really
fall in love ♪
[Pino sighs heavily]
♪ For you can't take
the chance ♪
Being a friend of yours.
dangerous business.
Well. that should
only make me stronger.
Sharpen my focus.
You know.
if you could package
and sell that confidence.
you'd have 'em
lined up down the block.
They already lined up down
the block for what I'm sellin'.
Well. you don't
have much left to sell.
and you don't have
a way to sell it.
I'm through with you.
Mr. Bernardi-
There's nothin' left to say.
She's leavin'.
Let's go.
[grave music playing]
Anybody who ever bet against me.
has lost.
You already lost.
And you can be goddamn certain.
that the house
is comin' to collect.
♪♪♪
We wanna get a look
in the trunk.
You're gonna need
a warrant for that.
Your brother's been
placed under arrest
for driving under the influence.
That allows us
full access to your vehicle.
Whoa.
Mr. Lawyer. you wanna
come here for a minute?
What's all this?
That shit ain't ours.
I don't know how it got there.
They know it was you.
The little girl didn't
identify you by name.
but she confirmed
that the perp was Black.
and they know you have a long
standing relationship with her.
[chuckles nervously]
Just cause I've been lookin'
after Amber.
don't mean I killed nobody.
Got me confused
with the wrong nigga.
They have two neighbors
that got a good look at you
exiting the home.
They feel confident
about their case.
Fuck their case.
As far as the three
of us are concerned.
this is it.
Like I told your daughter.
you stay outta my way.
I'll stay out of yours.
Juke lookin' all worried!
I'm good. I promise.
Those fools been chasin' me
since I could walk.
but I'm too fast. girl.
I'm Carl Moses out here.
[uneasy music playing]
[scooter engines revving]
Heard from Snaps and Pop that
you pressed up on that pimp
who been helpin'
your mom's move that work.
Guess you forgot
to hip me to that shit.
I mean. Stefano and all them
happy you did it.
You took out what was
left of Raq business.
who the fuck am I to beef
with you about it?
Wasn't really somethin'
I planned.
Kinda just showed itself to me.
so I made the move.
We got another move we
gon' need to make. nigga.
We gon' get a little messier
than runnin' up
in some white bitch apartment.
Especially for you.
Your name's come up
in another investigation.
Miss Thomas.
And while it doesn't fall under
Agent Tanner's purview.
you just might be able
to help him with his case.
which in turn could
help you with yours.
I don't need no help.
'cause y'all ain't got
no case against me.
Can you get specific
about this new and mysterious
investigation into my client?
Or are we just supposed
to take you at your word?
Miss Thomas recently sold
a piece of property
to an individual who's been
under investigation
for quite some time by the
Joint Terrorism Task Force.
We have reason to believe.
and a preponderance of evidence
that suggests. your client
was assisting said individual
in an elaborate money laundering
scheme.
You talkin' about
that bullshit mall?
I never even met
that motherfucker.
My broker set the whole shit up.
I just signed the papers.
Yeah. and you cashed the check.
We've been following you
for months. Miss Thomas.
We have surveillance
of you meeting with both
Stefano Marchetti and Pinot
Bernardi on multiple occasions.
Tell us the nature
of your relationships with them.
and there may be a discussion
to be had
about these money laundering
charges.
As of this moment. there are no
money laundering charges.
You could expect them.
I promise.
Fuck you and your promises.
I wouldn't be here
offering you a deal
if we didn't have you
dead to rights Miss Thomas.
I wouldn't waste my time.
But you are wasting your time
and mine.
[dramatic music playing]
I told 'em
that I'd take out Raq.
Ain't tryin' to put you
through all that.
Shit's a lot to ask.
I figured you and your mans
got beef already
after he knocked you
around like he did.
So you doin' him
make more sense.
Don't make as much sense
as you think.
So you wanna do Raq?
I'm just sayin'
I got more beef with her.
than I do with my uncle.
You gon' have to put down
one of 'em.
Snaps and Pop sayin' that they
need to see
that you dedicated.
Fuck them old ass niggas.
How 'bout they killed
my best friend
and I ain't takin' 'em
the fuck out for it?
That dedicated enough?
-How you hear that?
-Don't matter.
I know the shit's true.
but it don't matter.
And I don't give a fuck anyway.
You tell 'em I'll do this work.
but not cause I need
to prove shit to them
and nobody else.
I'm doin' it for me.
Fuck they talkin' about
after I left?
There's a money trail.
First off. the buyer paid
roughly thirty percent more
than the fair market value
for the property.
He paid what he
thought it was worth.
Fuck am I supposed to do?
Turn down the money?
You also paid your broker
a sizable amount of cash that
he gave back to the buyer.
to the F.B.I.
That looks to be
an obvious kickback.
That was his fee
for sellin' my shit.
Ain't my business what
he did with the money
after I gave it to him.
You paid your broker
significantly more
than what is considered
industry standard.
I told him if he sold it quick.
I hit him off
for something extra.
Unfortunately. that's not
what he told the F.B.I.
He said that this was an agreed
upon scheme between him.
you and the buyer.
Feds just cookin' up
this shit to get me to flip.
Maybe so.
But that doesn't change
our circumstance.
We're in a bad place here.
[foreboding music playing]
What's that all about?
Just countin' 'em up.
You countin' your gats.
Always good to know
what you got on hand.
What you want. Juke?
What you gonna do about
what Garcia was talkin' about?
I keep tellin' you.
I-I ain't worried about that.
All they got is the word of
some scared little white girl.
Well. scared little white girls
been killin' us forever.
Look. I appreciate you bein'
worried about me. but I'm good.
You're not.
And I don't know if it's
because you don't care
or you've given up
or you don't see it.
or maybe you don't
want to see it.
but everything goin' bad.
And I don't-I don't want
nothin' to happen to you.
I can't have nothin'
happen to you.
You always been here for me.
Just you.
Even through the bullshit.
we figured it out.
You figured it out.
And I'ma keep figurin' it out.
Always.
[gentle music playing]
["Hit It From The Back"
by Mobb Deep playing]
[Marvin]
We gettin' close to the spot.
tool the fuck up.
♪ I used to hit it raw daddy.
but now I carry packs of three ♪
♪ Bulletproof. I refuse to let
the monster get me ♪
♪ I'm in.
hit it from the back like that ♪
♪ Shorty Black never tap
no skins that look whack ♪
♪ I got mad game like Twister.
nasty little mister ♪
[Snaps] Heard you got something
you want to say to us. Kanan?
[Pops] We don't like to leave
shit unsaid. baby.
You don't like nothin' unsaid.
but you didn't say nothin'
though.
'bout puttin' down Fame.
You said it was
my moms who did it.
Somebody's feeding
you bad information. son.
We didn't have anything to do
with what happened
to your friend.
Why the fuck would we care
about what some stick-up kid
in Southside sayin'?
You thought he was
talkin' to the police?
And you knew me
and him was friends.
so you thought maybe
he was tellin' on y'all.
Who's sayin' this to you. Kanan?
Because whoever they are.
they have their own agenda.
They want to sow
dissension between us.
They tryin' to throw salt
in the game.
Turn us against each other.
It's a lie. son.
Baseless. contemptible.
shameful lies.
And frankly. it's disconcerting
that you believe 'em.
I mean. how we gon' be partners
if you don't trust us?
Maybe it wasn't y'all.
Shit. I don't even know.
[Snaps]
We know. It wasn't us.
But now. in light of
your accusations against us.
we're having a crisis of faith
when it comes to
you and your allegiance.
We need to know you
with us. baby.
We need to know you on our side.
Y'all want me to do
some real specific work.
Shit that's close to home.
And I'ma handle it.
Ain't none more loyal than that.
[tense music playing]
-[gunfire]
-[men shouting]
[Breeze] Y'all ain't shit.
bitch ass motherfuckers.
Show me somethin'.
[gunfire continues]
That all y'all got?
[grunting]
-[glass shatters]
-[groaning]
Where the fuck you think you
goin'. nigga?!
I ain't done with you.
-[glass shatters]
-[tires squeal]
Come back!
-Come back!
-[gunshots]
[yelling]
We was havin' fun!
Bitch ass niggas!
[gunshots]
[gun clip clicks]
[knocking on door]
I just want to talk to you
for a minute. that's all.
Look. I know you said that
we can't be together.
but I need you in my life. Juke.
I can't think about
nothin' else.
My grades are all fucked up.
I stopped talkin' to
all my friends.
My eatin' shit is back.
I miss you so fucking much.
Mm.
I'm with somebody else now.
Bullshit.
The girl I met at the club.
I know what you doin'. juke.
I'm not stupid.
You lyin' to me because
you tryin' to protect me.
but I don't need you
to do that. okay?
I can take care of myself.
I'd rather be with you
and take the chance
that some ill shit
might happen to me
than to not be with you
and end up hatin'
my whole damn life.
Juke. I...
[tense music playing]
What the fuck is this?
Look like a gat to me. Iesha.
What it look like to you?
Is it yours?
It is.
[dramatic music playing]
Still wanna take that chance
bein' with me?
Time to go.
Go. Iesha!
[dramatic music playing]
♪♪♪
Whatever the fuck
you about to do.
before you do it.
you need to hear
that I love you. Juke.
You need to know
that I won't make it
if anything happens to you.
♪♪♪
Kanan wasn't there?
[Raq exhales heavily]
This nigga Breeze a problem.
But we got answers.
Ain't no different than all the
niggas that came before him.
DefCon. High Post. even 'Nique.
And where the fuck are they now?
They gone and we still here.
And Breeze just the same
as all of 'em.
And he gonna go out
just like them too.
Maybe he the same.
but we different.
I don't know if it's
'cause we aged out the game
or 'cause we lost our way.
But the streets
ain't ours no more.
and we ain't gettin' 'em back.
Well. as long as we got work.
we got the streets. Marvin.
And we still got product
from Joaquin and Hafiz left.
We can be back up in a hour.
We marks out here.
Them Italians and Kafghans
comin' for us.
We gonna find our way.
We always do.
Can I ask you somethin'
without you gettin'
all mad at me and shit?
Depend on the question.
When we first started out.
it was all about money and rep.
It's about walkin' down
the block
and havin' fools
get the fuck out of the way
'cause they knew
you was that nigga.
'Cause they knew
you were certified.
'Cause they knew you handled
your fuckin' business.
And that shit felt good.
And that was the most fuckin'
fun I ever had.
But even after we got all
that. it wasn't enough.
We wasn't satisfied like
we thought we would be.
And so we got more.
And more.
And even more after that.
But the more we got.
the more we seen.
it just was never
gon' be enough.
It was like the harder
we chased the shit.
the more it got away from us.
The money and the work.
Ain't never gon' fix
what's wrong. Raq.
Ain't never gonna fill
the hole in our fuckin' hearts.
And the hole in your heart
is Kanan.
Breeze.
Stefano. 'Nique...
none of them niggas
matter to you.
Truth is.
Me and Lou don't really mean
nothin' to you neither.
That's not true.
Somehow you got in your head
that you doin' all this shit.
is gonna get your son
to love you.
Or at least get him to see you
how you want him to see you.
But it won't.
'Cause Kanan.
just like the game:
The more you push.
the further away
that shit gon' get.
[melancholy music playing]
She got a gun. I saw it.
We all got guns.
and the shit was
probably Marvin's anyway.
I'm tellin' you. she's gon' do
somethin' crazy. Kanan.
You gotta go check on her.
Me and Juke ain't really
talkin' right now.
And if she is plannin'
somethin' crazy with that gat.
most likely she comin' for me.
so you should probably get
the fuck out of here.
Don't even joke like that.
I don't even know
if that shits a joke.
I got shit to do.
You gotta bounce. Iesha.
Thomases always kickin' me out.
Somehow you still not gettin'
the fuckin' message.
[Pops] What are you gonna say
to Breeze?
I'm gonna say to him exactly
what the fuck he needs to hear.
We would have done the same shit
when we was his age.
I stood by my word then.
just like I stand on it now.
Nobody should know that
better than my wife.
[dramatic music playing]
♪♪♪
Follow them.
[Tramont] You got to be
out your fuckin' mind.
You really askin' me
to break you off some work
after all the shit you did?
You went around me.
I came at you.
You know how it work.
It don't work
like you think it do.
Hell. if it wasn't for all
these witnesses around here.
I'd put a fuckin' bullet in you
myself right now.
This nigga feelin'
all bold and sassy.
It wasn't long ago you was ready
to suck my brother's dick
to let you live.
Someone need to let
your mouth know
it don't have the muscle to
back up all that talk no more.
Everyone know
you out here alone.
You as good as dead.
And I'ma piss on your grave.
girl.
Count on that shit.
[tense music playing]
♪♪♪
Thank you.
[dramatic music playing]
Is unconscionable. nigga.
We stake you. we protect you-
hell. we damn near raise you-
and yet you fuck us.
It ain't even like that.
though. Snaps.
Shit just some Alize money.
Little somethin'-somethin' to
buy some drinks up in the club.
Yeah. but you gonna trade that
Alize in for pruno. nigga.
because them white boys.
they dimed you the fuck out.
Turned state's evidence
on your Black ass.
I got that. You don't need
to worry about them.
We warned you.
Told you not to have
no side business again.
Everything aboveboard.
But you and all your stupidness
couldn't help yourself.
Fool me once: Shame on you.
Fool me twice: Fuck you nigga.
I'm gonna make this right.
Let me give you all I made
off that pill bullshit.
Too late for that. son.
Your services
are no longer required.
You bein' replaced.
We'll alert
the relevant parties.
Who the fuck gonna replace me?!
I ain't the kind of nigga
you could just replace!
[subway brakes squealing]
[doorbell rings]
May I help you?
I'm lookin' for Pernessa?
Who are you?
I'm a friend of Pernessa
and Unique.
What's your name?
[unsettling music playing]
You're Raq.
I know exactly who you are.
I've heard all about you.
You need to get off my stoop
before I call the police.
I just want to talk to 'Nique.
that's all.
Oh. well. my daughter
and Kadeem have left New York.
and they're never comin' back.
So you can't do
anything to them.
If you come around here again.
I got a gun of my own.
and I know how to use it.
[door slams]
♪♪♪
For real. though. who we got
to step up for Breeze?
We got you and me.
Fuck callin' in plays
from the goddamn sidelines.
Time to suit the fuck up
and get back on the field.
[menacing music playing]
You killed Famous.
[tense music playing]
Kanan's cousin.
This shit again.
We didn't kill that boy.
sweetheart.
We don't even know him.
Police told me you dropped him.
Ah.
-They lyin' to you. girl.
-[gunshots]
[ominous music playing]
♪♪♪
[gunshot]
[case clicks shut]
[menacing music playing]
♪♪♪
[knocking on door]
[Zeke clears throat]
Your niece here.
I know you didn't kill Famous.
[dramatic music playing]
If somethin' happens to me.
you gotta get this
to my daughter.
That sounds ominous.
I just need you
to do this for me.
I can't be party
to anything illegal.
Nothin' in there's gonna be
a problem for the police or God.
But if any of it go missin'.
that gonna be a problem for you.
This for your time
and wisdom and all that.
We'll consider this a tithe.
Call it whatever you want.
Just make sure that case
get to my daughter.
I'm gonna take this
to the parsonage
next door for safekeeping.
Don't go anywhere.
I want to continue
this conversation.
[footsteps departing]
[ominous music playing]
[heavy footsteps returning]
You move fast. pastor.
Fuck you doin' here?
[menacing music playing]
[scoffs]
This underhanded nigga
robbin' churches now.
I ain't here to rob nobody.
Uncle Marvin.
Oh. shit.
For real?
This cause I knocked
your punk ass around
for what you did to your uncle?
It's bigger than that.
Ain't nothin' bigger
than that. nigga.
Relax. nigga.
I'm just gettin' a smoke.
I'ma light this shit on fire.
[lighter sparks]
[Marvin sighs deeply]
This gon' stay with you
for a while. boy.
You gon' see me
in your nightmares?
I'll be aight.
You won't.
Not at first.
You gonna get there.
but that's only 'cause you
gonna be so dead inside by then.
you ain't gon' feel
nothin' no more anyway.
That how it happened for you?
I'm not low down like you.
Kanan.
You don't care about nobody
but yourself.
That's why you gon' die alone.
nigga.
Ain't nobody gon' miss you.
'cause you ain't gon'
have nobody left.
We doin' this or what?
Pastor gon' be here soon.
If you gon' do it.
fuckin' do what you gon...
[gunshots]
♪♪♪
[grave music playing]
[older Kanan]
If you didn't hate me before.
you hate me now.
And I don't give a fuck. nigga.
♪♪♪
["Little Ghetto Boy"
by Donny Hathaway playing]
♪ Little ghetto boy ♪
♪ Playing in the ghetto street ♪
♪ What'cha gonna do
when you grown up ♪
♪ And have to face
responsibility? ♪
♪ Will you spend your days
and nights in a pool room? ♪
♪ Will you sell caps of
madness to the neighborhood? ♪
♪ Little ghetto boy ♪
♪ You already know
how rough life can be ♪
♪ 'Cause you've seen ♪
♪ So much pain and misery ♪
♪ Little ghetto boy ♪
♪ Your daddy was blown away ♪
♪ He robbed that grocery store ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm